允许谈论阵列。
Lets talk about arrays.
我不是在说你在报酬审查中想要的东西
And I'm not talking about the thing you
want at your compensation review of
在没有困难的人群之后的那一年
the year possible after
nothing tough crowd.
也许是个艰难的问题
Maybe is a hard question.
对数据结构进行数组。
Arrays the data structure.
有多种方法可以将项转换为数组，因此如果我有一个对象
There are many ways to convert an item
into array, so if I have an object I can
调用 object.entries() 将为我提供数组数组。
call object.entries() that will
give me an array of arrays.
其中数组中的第一个对象是或
Where the first object in the array is or
索引为零的第一个条目是键，有一个值。
the first entry at index zero is the key,
there was the value.
其实这应该是我一直在用的
Actually and this is should be
something I use all the time.
如果你想把钥匙取出来你会说 object.keys 和
If you wanna just get the keys out,
you say object.keys and
用于对对象进行迭代。
use that to iterate over an object.
你可以说 array.from.
You can say array.from.
它将采用类似于数组的对象。
It will take an array-like object.
因此函数自变量是类似于数组的对象。
So function arguments
are an array-like object.
它们不是一个阵列，但它们看起来像一个，如果你转换成一个阵列，
They're not an array but they look like
one, and if you convert into an array,
您可以对其使用数组方法。
you can use array methods on it.
另一个是什么
What's another one?
HTML 元素或子代，类似的内容，不一定是数组，但是
HTML elements or children, things
like that, not necessarily arrays but
你可以操纵一个有 arrayy的人
you can manipulate one with array.from.
你也可以用传播
You could also use spread or
任何能够迭代的迭代都是迭代的，其他数组是可迭代的。
whatever iterable that you want so strings
are iterable, other arrays are iterable.
这只会把这只奇怪的量传播到一个数组中。
This just spreads this
odd amount into an array.
所以这些是进入一个阵列的方法。
So these are ways to get to an array.
我找到的有用的方法
Useful methods that I find.
这里有很多
There's a lot.
我可以把全部名单都做得非常有用
I could actually do the entire list
cuz they're all pretty useful.
阵列 .isArray 很有用，因为如果您一直在执行 JavaScript ，
Array .isArray is useful because if
you've been doing JavaScript a while,
发现什么是阵列其实是个难题
finding out if something's an array
was actually a hard problem.
因为阵列不是一个类型，所以你不能只进行类型的排列，
You couldn't actually do just type
of array because array's not a type,
数组将作为对象返回。
array would come back just as objects.
因此，数组 .isArray 非常有用。
So array .isArray is extremely useful.
过滤，减少， concat， join， pop， push 我不太投入这些和假定
Filter, reduce, concat, join, pop, push I
won't go too much into these and assuming
如果你知道的话你可能以前见过的一些 JavaScript
if you know, a little bit JavaScript
you probably have seen these before.
但重要的是了解这些方法
But what's important to know about
these is which of these methods
你的重重者不会再回来了
return in your re which of them don't.
所以，过滤，给我一个昨天的新阵列。
So filter, just give me a yesterday
returns a new array are now.
>> 是。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
>> 是，它会减少。
&gt;&gt; Yes, it does reduce.
>> 是。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
>> 减少棘手的问题，减少返回任何希望返回的内容
&gt;&gt; Reduces the tricky one, reduce will
return anything you want to return you
要返回对象，它将返回要打开阵列的对象，
want to return objects,it will return
an object you want to turn an array,
它将返回一个数组。
it will return an array.
任何你想要的东西都会回来的
It will return pretty much
anything you want whatsoever.
这是我最喜欢的方法之一
This is one of my favorite
methods of all time.
我可以用一个减速器和一个减速器来做任何你想做的事
I can do almost anything you want to
do in JavaScript with a reducer and
这就是着名的地图被缩小的原因
that's why the famous map reduce, there's
the map part at radial or something and
然后将其减少到要获取的对象。
then reducing it down to
the object you want to get.
这大概是我们制作的 50% 的节目
That's probably like 50%
of programming that we do,
如果你真的很诚实的话
if you're like being really honest.
另外 50% 只是从数据库中读取一些东西。
The other 50% is just reading
something from a database.
我是认真的
I'm totally serious.
就像想想你的工作是什么，这可能是什么。
[LAUGH] Like think about what your job
is and that's probably what it is.
它减少了某些东西，并从数据库中读取一些东西。
It's reducing something and
reading something from a database.
Concat 会返回新数组还是否?
Concat returns a new array or no?
是的是的
Yes, it does.
它将连接两个阵列。
It will join two arrays.
它会加入它实际上如果你承认一个函数
It will join, it will actually
if you concat a function and
如果您想要，可以将函数添加到数组的末尾。
you can add a function onto an end
of the array if you wanted to.
老爸
Pop?
没有从数组中返回第一个项的弹出窗口。
No pop returns that first
item from the array.
它只返回一个项目。
It just returns an item.
它不会返回阵列。
It doesn't return the array.
推我推 它什么都不回
Push.
It doesn't return anything.
这只是一种方法
It's just a method.
映射，它会返回新的数组。
Map, it does return a new array.
好了现在你知道这些方法了
All right, so now you know these methods.
你不必像你的手那样了解他们
You don't have to know them
like the back of your hand.
奇怪，但我建议至少知道其中一些。
Weird, but I do recommend
knowing at least some of these.
你想做什么都能用数组来做
Cuz again, almost anything you wanna
do you can do it with an array.
只要你知道怎么把东西转换成一个阵列
As long as you know how to
convert something into an array.
您可以开始使用这些操作。
You can start manipulating with these.